[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "What makes this different to \"Idol\"?", "question_tokens": ["What", "makes", "this", "different", "to", "``", "Idol", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "It's -- you know, it's difficult to say until you actually make the show.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "difficult", "to", "say", "until", "you", "actually", "make", "the", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Why is this a different show?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "this", "a", "different", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "You can be 12.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "be", "12", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Is that going to be a key weapon do you think in your ratings and so on \"X Factor America\"?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "going", "to", "be", "a", "key", "weapon", "do", "you", "think", "in", "your", "ratings", "and", "so", "on", "``", "X", "Factor", "America", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, you're quite.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'re", "quite", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "So you can see who are the real performers, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "can", "see", "who", "are", "the", "real", "performers", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Well, look, where they start is where you want them to end up.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "where", "they", "start", "is", "where", "you", "want", "them", "to", "end", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Why did you take this huge gamble?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "take", "this", "huge", "gamble", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "OWELL: Because I made, you know, a lot of money.", "answer_tokens": ["OWELL", ":", "Because", "I", "made", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "When did you get bored being -- what was a highly paid performing monkey in the end?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "get", "bored", "being", "--", "what", "was", "a", "highly", "paid", "performing", "monkey", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Can we?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I'm sorry, you don't have any control.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "control", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "You're a monkey.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "monkey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "It's a gamble, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "gamble", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "It has to be a gamble.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "has", "to", "be", "a", "gamble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Has any part of you contemplated the unthinkable?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "any", "part", "of", "you", "contemplated", "the", "unthinkable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Always.", "answer_tokens": ["Always", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Would you accept that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "accept", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "What was it like for you that moment, honestly, when you realized that was it, you were walking away from the show that had made you a global superstar?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "for", "you", "that", "moment", ",", "honestly", ",", "when", "you", "realized", "that", "was", "it", ",", "you", "were", "walking", "away", "from", "the", "show", "that", "had", "made", "you", "a", "global", "superstar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "I got really emotional, I mean genuinely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "really", "emotional", ",", "I", "mean", "genuinely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Any tears that night?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "tears", "that", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "I kind of welled up a bit, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "kind", "of", "welled", "up", "a", "bit", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Did you think it was a mistake to get rid of Paula?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "it", "was", "a", "mistake", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "Paula", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Certainly.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "ORGAN: What do you think of Steven Tyler and J. Lo?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Steven", "Tyler", "and", "J.", "Lo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Good.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steven Tyler"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Does that make you laugh?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "make", "you", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Hilarious.", "answer_tokens": ["Hilarious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "I can't imagine it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "imagine", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Is it fame, power, or money?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "fame", ",", "power", ",", "or", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Well, I can tell you now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Should we go back to the fame and power?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "we", "go", "back", "to", "the", "fame", "and", "power", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Yes, but you wouldn't do it for nothing, would you?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "you", "would", "n't", "do", "it", "for", "nothing", ",", "would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Yes, for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJS", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "What advice did your parents give you then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "did", "your", "parents", "give", "you", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "They were really -- you know, honest to god, they were just cool about it.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "were", "really", "--", "you", "know", ",", "honest", "to", "god", ",", "they", "were", "just", "cool", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "If that wasn't the worst time in your life, what was?", "question_tokens": ["If", "that", "was", "n't", "the", "worst", "time", "in", "your", "life", ",", "what", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "When my dad died was the worst time in my life, as you know.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "my", "dad", "died", "was", "the", "worst", "time", "in", "my", "life", ",", "as", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin Firth"]}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NN", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 401, "question": "What's the problem?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "problem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "It's really like Colin Firth and the (INAUDIBLE) and the fountain in \"Bridget Jones.\"", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "really", "like", "Colin", "Firth", "and", "the", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "and", "the", "fountain", "in", "``", "Bridget", "Jones", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Fighting, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Fighting", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "What was that day like for you when you look back on it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "day", "like", "for", "you", "when", "you", "look", "back", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "I can't lie.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "lie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "What was the best advice he gave you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "best", "advice", "he", "gave", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Best advice.", "answer_tokens": ["Best", "advice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "She is probably the only woman I know who actually has any kind of control over you, isn't she?", "question_tokens": ["She", "is", "probably", "the", "only", "woman", "I", "know", "who", "actually", "has", "any", "kind", "of", "control", "over", "you", ",", "is", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "We fight.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "What was it about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Honestly, I can't remember, Piers, but I'm now 12 years old, I'm not going to say sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["Honestly", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "remember", ",", "Piers", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "now", "12", "years", "old", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "say", "sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "You're quite a mommy's boy, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "quite", "a", "mommy", "'s", "boy", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Well, not exactly, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "exactly", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "When you're in England, you have Sunday lunch with her almost every Sunday, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "in", "England", ",", "you", "have", "Sunday", "lunch", "with", "her", "almost", "every", "Sunday", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Well, she comes up to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "comes", "up", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday", "Sunday"], "LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Is it going to happen to us?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "going", "to", "happen", "to", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "I hope not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last year"]}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Is it the -- is the intense attention now from the Internet, from TMZ, from -- has the game changed for celebrities?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "the", "--", "is", "the", "intense", "attention", "now", "from", "the", "Internet", ",", "from", "TMZ", ",", "from", "--", "has", "the", "game", "changed", "for", "celebrities", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "I was -- I was talking to a friend of mine last year where we had this conversation where everything got a bit bleak last year.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "I", "was", "talking", "to", "a", "friend", "of", "mine", "last", "year", "where", "we", "had", "this", "conversation", "where", "everything", "got", "a", "bit", "bleak", "last", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["TMZ"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Didn't you get offered some huge six figure sum by a guy in a restaurant in L.A. once?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "you", "get", "offered", "some", "huge", "six", "figure", "sum", "by", "a", "guy", "in", "a", "restaurant", "in", "L.A.", "once", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Yes, he offered me I think it was 150,000 grand to criticize him bonking his wife.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "offered", "me", "I", "think", "it", "was", "150,000", "grand", "to", "criticize", "him", "bonking", "his", "wife", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Why wouldn't you do that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "n't", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Because -- no.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "--", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "If you're watching, I'll even do it for 50,000 dollars, OK?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "watching", ",", "I", "'ll", "even", "do", "it", "for", "50,000", "dollars", ",", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "And was it going to be that night.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "was", "it", "going", "to", "be", "that", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["50,000 dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "The what?", "question_tokens": ["The", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "-- the boudoir.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "the", "boudoir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Do you think you're a bit of a sex god?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "sex", "god", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "A sex god -- boudoir.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "sex", "god", "--", "boudoir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "What is happening to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "happening", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Let's take the boy out of the tabloids.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "take", "the", "boy", "out", "of", "the", "tabloids", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VB", ",", "``", "NNP", "''", ":"], "qSentId": 549, "question": "A sex god?", "question_tokens": ["A", "sex", "god", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I just wondered do you look in the mirror sometimes and think, \"Whoa\"--", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "wondered", "do", "you", "look", "in", "the", "mirror", "sometimes", "and", "think", ",", "``", "Whoa", "''", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "No seriously?", "question_tokens": ["No", "seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Hmm.", "answer_tokens": ["Hmm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Do you care that it's shallow?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "care", "that", "it", "'s", "shallow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "I like it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Where are you getting your language from today?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "getting", "your", "language", "from", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I'm on CNN now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "on", "CNN", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Are you going to the royal wedding?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "the", "royal", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I haven't been invited.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "been", "invited", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "What do you think of William and Kate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "William", "and", "Kate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "I don't know William.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "William", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate?"], "LOCATION": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "I can't believe in America they're going crazy for it, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "believe", "in", "America", "they", "'re", "going", "crazy", "for", "it", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Yes, well you think -- I -- I can remember those awful shots as the two of them, you know, on -- on -- on the funeral.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", "you", "think", "--", "I", "--", "I", "can", "remember", "those", "awful", "shots", "as", "the", "two", "of", "them", ",", "you", "know", ",", "on", "--", "on", "--", "on", "the", "funeral", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Are you a monarchist?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "monarchist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "WDT", ":", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Do you believe in the institution of monarchy, unelected?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "in", "the", "institution", "of", "monarchy", ",", "unelected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "I -- I -- I do -- certainly for our own country I do, because I think it -- it's just something which -- which makes us unique.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "--", "I", "do", "--", "certainly", "for", "our", "own", "country", "I", "do", ",", "because", "I", "think", "it", "--", "it", "'s", "just", "something", "which", "--", "which", "makes", "us", "unique", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "I mean, do you sing?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "sing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Do you dance?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "dance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Not well.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Do you do impressions?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "do", "impressions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Badly.", "answer_tokens": ["Badly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Can you act?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "act", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Can you do trapeze acts?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "do", "trapeze", "acts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Juggling?", "question_tokens": ["Juggling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Managed that a few times.", "answer_tokens": ["Managed", "that", "a", "few", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Fire eating?", "question_tokens": ["Fire", "eating", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "At times.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "-- what would you declare as your talent, if you had to?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "would", "you", "declare", "as", "your", "talent", ",", "if", "you", "had", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "ORGAN: Or paying of death, what would you say you -- was your talent?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Or", "paying", "of", "death", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "you", "--", "was", "your", "talent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "I'm good at spotting somebody else's talent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "at", "spotting", "somebody", "else", "'s", "talent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Apart from that, what is the -- what is the tangible talent?", "question_tokens": ["Apart", "from", "that", ",", "what", "is", "the", "--", "what", "is", "the", "tangible", "talent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "That's it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Yes, but if you had to?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "if", "you", "had", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Oh, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "If you had to produce your own talent, do you have a secret one we don't know about?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "to", "produce", "your", "own", "talent", ",", "do", "you", "have", "a", "secret", "one", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "High diving.", "answer_tokens": ["High", "diving", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "He's cool, right?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "cool", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "He's this high.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "this", "high", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "What do you make of him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "I think he's -- I think he's really talented, really musical.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "--", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "really", "talented", ",", "really", "musical", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "And how old are you, Susan?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "old", "are", "you", ",", "Susan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "I am 47.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "47", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VBG", "``", "PRP", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "''", "IN", "``", "NNS", "VBZ", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 725, "question": "What are you going to sing tonight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "going", "to", "sing", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "I'm going to sing \"I Dreamed A Dream\" from \"Les Miserables.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "sing", "``", "I", "Dreamed", "A", "Dream", "''", "from", "``", "Les", "Miserables", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "And we both thought this was a preposterous moment where this little old lady from -- or middle aged lady from Scotland was just going to come on and be a complete train wreck, didn't we?", "question_tokens": ["And", "we", "both", "thought", "this", "was", "a", "preposterous", "moment", "where", "this", "little", "old", "lady", "from", "--", "or", "middle", "aged", "lady", "from", "Scotland", "was", "just", "going", "to", "come", "on", "and", "be", "a", "complete", "train", "wreck", ",", "did", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", ":", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Scotland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "Wasn't it amazing?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "it", "amazing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "I mean, how can that be a bad thing?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "can", "that", "be", "a", "bad", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "Elton John gave you a bit of a whack the other day.", "answer_tokens": ["Elton", "John", "gave", "you", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "whack", "the", "other", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "What did he say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "He said -- similar kind of thing.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "said", "--", "similar", "kind", "of", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "Why do they say bad things about me?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "they", "say", "bad", "things", "about", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "We're going to come back after another short break.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "going", "to", "come", "back", "after", "another", "short", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "But I've gone a little bit further this time, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["But", "I", "'ve", "gone", "a", "little", "bit", "further", "this", "time", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "Go on.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "Five million?", "question_tokens": ["Five", "million", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "Five million.", "answer_tokens": ["Five", "million", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "That's your show as well?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "your", "show", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "No, I know.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "Do you think you're going to get the same kind of success in America?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "get", "the", "same", "kind", "of", "success", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "I don't think that shows in general have produced enough global stars, if I'm being honest with you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "shows", "in", "general", "have", "produced", "enough", "global", "stars", ",", "if", "I", "'m", "being", "honest", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 837, "question": "And what about a host?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "about", "a", "host", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 838, "answer": "We're looking.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "looking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 839, "question": "I was wondering if you've chosen one yet?", "question_tokens": ["I", "was", "wondering", "if", "you", "'ve", "chosen", "one", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 840, "answer": "Yes, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 841, "question": "Have you?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 842, "answer": "I've got an idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "got", "an", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 853, "question": "So be -- it's going to be two people?", "question_tokens": ["So", "be", "--", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "two", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 854, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "Are they American?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "American", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "Two American -- man, woman?", "question_tokens": ["Two", "American", "--", "man", ",", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNP", ":", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 870, "question": "Have you thought about it?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "thought", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 871, "answer": "Well, I think I'm good at it, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "I", "'m", "good", "at", "it", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 891, "question": "How can they join in the X-Factor party in America?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "they", "join", "in", "the", "X-Factor", "party", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 892, "answer": "Well -- well, we start in Los Angeles at the Sports Arena.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--", "well", ",", "we", "start", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "at", "the", "Sports", "Arena", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "These are without the judges, right?", "question_tokens": ["These", "are", "without", "the", "judges", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "These are without the judges.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "are", "without", "the", "judges", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "Are you nervous?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "nervous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 915, "question": "Do you really?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 916, "answer": "Not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]